♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked
him on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him into space ♪
♪ Let me out ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
♪ Where the movies
begin or end ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help of
his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call ♪
♪ Cambot ♪
♪ Gypsy ♪
♪ Tom Servo ♪
♪ Croooow ♪
- That's one O.
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery
Science Theater 3000♪
(slamming doors)
(electronic beeping)
- Oh, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, I see, yes.
Well, describe your
childhood to me Mr. T Robot.
- I didn't have a childhood.
- Mm, I see.
How would you describe your
relationship with your mother?
- I didn't have a mother.
- Oh, interesting.
Have you seen "Cliffhanger?"
- No.
- Hm, tell me more about that.
- I didn't see "Cliffhanger."
- Well this seems
painful to you.
- No.
- Hm, not tell me Crow T.
what kind of fishing lure
do you think is appropriate
for early spring?
- Definitely a Rebel D, uh,
nothing leaves
this office right?
- Mr. Robot, everything
said here today
is strictly confidential.
- Definitely a Rebel Deep
Diving lure for early spring.
- Yes, yes, ah well, I
see our time is up, Crow.
We'll be right back.
- What?
- I'm prescribing a
series of commercials.
- Oh!
(light music)
Gee, I feel kind of
embarrassed about
the things I told
you in our session.
- Don't worry Crow,
as I said before
whatever you tell
me in the privacy
of my office is in the
strictest of confidence.
- Hi guys.
- Say Mike, you
won't believe some
of the weird stuff this
nut cup is into here.
- Hey!
- You know that he uses
a Rebel Deep Diving lure
in early spring?
- I don't, I lied about that.
It was no, shh, hey.
(laughing)
(muttering)
- Oh, you'll have to excuse me.
Things have been a little
hectic down here this week.
You see my mother's
coming to visit
and well, we've
redecorated in her honor.
She's the one person in
my life who's responsible
for my deep psychological
scar and naturally
I wanted the place
to look nice for her.
Oh, I'm going to send
you along some material
that I want you to say to
her when she gets here.
If you do a good job
and I'll show you
my appreciation by
not killing you.
Frank!
- Relax, Clay everything's
under control.
Look, I made your mother
this nice fruit bowl.
No oranges, though.
Your mother can't have oranges.
The citric acid gives her gas.
- Oh, that's a very good
point, Frank, because.
How do you know so
much about my mother?
- Well, I've been corresponding
with her regularly
for quite some time now.
I thought you knew that.
- No I.
(ringing doorbell)
Oh, that's her.
Come in!
Mother!
- It is so wonderful to see you.
(kissing)
- You look fabulous.
- Oh, thank you for
the lovely card.
That was so thoughtful of you.
We have so much to talk about.
Before we talk about
anything else though,
there is one thing I have got
to tell you about and that--
- Wait, wait, let me guess.
Meg Anderson's party.
(chuckling)
- Well, you're not
gonna believe it
but I wore the blue dress.
- You didn't!
- I most certainly
did and you should
have seen it when I--
- Mother?
- What?
- Some friends of
mine have put together
a little presentation
in your honor.
I told them not to but they,
they're a bunch
of knuckle heads.
Well, you know, let's watch huh?
- Hi Clayton, oh I see
that your mother is here.
It's great to finally
meet the mother
of such a good friend of mine.
Many is the time you
and I have engaged
in spirited hi jinks.
I enjoy your company
very, very much.
- Oh, I hope your
visit from your mother
doesn't interfere with your
brilliant science experiments
when the history of the 20th
century is ultimately written
the name of one man will
tower above all others.
That man is you.
Dr. Clayton Forrester, there.
- Dr. Clayton Forrester.
You have made the
world a better place.
By staying under ground.
I can't believe this.
Who wrote this junk?
This is so stupid.
- Dr. Forrester, perhaps
no other individual
embodies the style,
panache, and verve
of the elegant sport
of polo more than you.
Your, oh I can't do this.
- Honey.
- Mrs. Forrester,
your son is sick!
He's sick!
- She's just.
- You need serious help.
If there's anything you can do
to help him you should really.
- Well I guess there's
really not much left to say
other than your movie this
week is called "Blood Lust!"
it's immediately preceded
by a short called
"A Visit to Uncle Jim's Farm."
I never visited my uncle.
After all, a boy's best
friend is his mother.
- Yes.
- Now I understand
why he's so sick.
Boy, I'm tempted to
call her something
that rhymes with bitch.
Oh, I mean, switch.
- She said the word!
- I know what you meant.
Oh my god, movie time.
- [Crow] Gypsy's in
trouble, Gypsy's in trouble.
(beeping)
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] You have to spank it.
- [Mike] No, you can't say that.
- [Crow] Can we say it now?
- [Mike] No, you can't say it.
- [Tom] I'm Dairy
Council intolerant.
- [Mike] Is Velveeta a member
of the National Dairy Council?
- [Tom] No, Velveeta's
a splinter group.
- [Crow] I though I
smelled something.
- [Tom] Yes, the farm
of secrets and lies.
- [Mike] Ladies and
gentlemen, Mrs. Loretta Doyle.
♪ I was warned as a child♪
- [Narrator] This
is a story about
the summer George and Betty
spent on Uncle Jim's dairy farm.
- [Tom] A cautionary tale.
- [Narrator] George and
Betty are both excited
because this is a
very special trip.
- [Crow] They're
dropping off the kids
and never coming back.
- [Narrator] But they're
not a bit more excited
than Andy and Jane,
who live on the farm.
- [Tom] Poor saps.
- Jane, I think they're here.
I see their car.
- Are you sure?
- [Crow] Don't ever question me.
- Sure, I'm sure.
- I'll run tell mom.
Mom, mom.
- [Tom] Hey, (giggling).
- [Crow] Here in
frame 54 Mr. Connally
is struck by the bullet.
- [Narrator] No wonder
they're all so excited.
After Uncle Fred and Aunt
Alice go back to the city
George and Betty
are going to stay.
To spend a whole
summer on the farm
with Jane and Andy.
- Where's Uncle Jim?
- Dad's out in
the field, come on
and I'll let you ring
the bell to call him.
- Okay!
- [Tom] Let's go
tip some cattle!
- Go on Betty, you ring it.
- [Mike] Ah yes,
the bell signals
a nuclear attack in these parts.
- [Crow] Well now they have
nothing to look forward to.
- [Tom] I never want
this day to end.
(ringing bell)
- [Crow] Well what'd
ya know, someone fell
in the thresher again.
Already the children
have disturbed Uncle Jim.
Uncle Jim is an edgy man
who should not be riled.
- [Tom] Gange, Betty?
- [Narrator] The grown ups
have things to talk about
but Andy and Jane have
their plans all set.
The first thing to do is
to show their city cousins
some new things around the farm.
- [Mike] Their throats
tightened with apprehension.
- [Narrator] And because
it is a dairy farm
the first thing they show off--
- [Tom] Oh bossy.
- [Crow] Oh, nothing,
I'm not doing anything!
- [Narrator] Where
their older brother Bill
has started the milking.
- How are ya?
- We're fine!
My, it's clean in here.
- That's right, Betty.
All dairy farms want to
keep their barns clean
and their cows too.
- Is that why you're
washing the cow?
- Every morning and
evening, George,
just before they're milked.
This is one way we help
to make sure the milk
is always pure and wholesome,
and good tasting, too.
- [Tom] Go on, taste her.
- See those pipes up there?
The milk runs from the
cow, through those pipes
to a big cooler
in the milk room.
- Yeah, so it keeps
cold and fresh until we.
- [Mike] Uh, excuse
me back here.
I need some help back
here I got some pot in my.
- Uncle Jim, how
do cows make milk?
- Oh they make it
out of what they eat.
- Yes, but what do they eat?
- Well come on, I'll show you.
- [Crow] The kids feign interest
so as not rile Uncle Jim.
- [Tom] You see, we dump
this stuff in the creek
and the government
pays us for it.
- Wow, look at it all come out.
- [Crow] I just saw a finger.
- [Mike] Can we go home?
- Now this is what the
cows eat at milking time.
- [Tom] Pure, uncut.
- [Mike] The first
one's free, kid.
- Why that looks like some
of our breakfast cereal.
(chuckling)
- Well that's pretty
much what it is, Betty.
As a matter of fact, cows
are a lot like people.
- [Crow] They're sinners.
- Now this feed is a special
mixture of ground grain
with the extra
vitamins and minerals
that cows must eat
to stay healthy.
Of course they eat grass
and hay and silage too.
They eat all different
kinds of good food.
Plenty of good, clean water,
and a clean, comfortable
place to live.
That way they grow to
be strong and healthy.
- [Crow] When we slaughter them.
- Help your brother
Bill with the milking.
You know Andy, I think
that maybe Betty and George
would like to see the hay loft.
What'd ya think, huh?
- [Children] Yeah!
(chuckling)
- [Mike] Not really, is
there anything on TV?
- [Tom] Now junior samples
of Lulu Bill make
their appearance.
(upbeat music)
- [Crow] Oh my spine!
I don't think, 'cause
my doctor, I'm frail
and I have allergy but
if you really want me to.
(crunching)
Oh, I fell on the
pitch fork I'm.
(upbeat music)
- [Mike] All the commotion
provokes a bull snake
resting in the hay.
- [Tom] I gotta be
careful of my new jeans
because I got them at Pamida.
- [Mike] Tonight on ESPN2,
hayloft rope swinging.
- [Crow] You better watch
because it might happen.
This is when you get
that tingly feeling.
- [Tom] It's easier
when a stage hand helps.
(cheering)
- Hooray for Andy.
- Okay George it's your turn.
(children cheering)
- [Mike] The summer of
my German humiliation.
- I can't do it.
- Come on.
(children cheering)
- [Mike] But I want to
write poetry and act.
- I can't do it.
- That's okay, George.
You can't do it now but the
bigger and stronger you get
and the more you practice
the more things you can do.
You'll be able to do it
by the end of the summer.
- [Crow] Now give
me 30, solider.
- [Narrator] George and
Betty soon discovered
that on a farm everybody
has work to do.
- [Tom] Miss Curtsy
does the typing.
- [Narrator] Right now this
new calf doesn't need any help.
It's just two days old but it
knows where it's dinner is.
- [Crow] Hey, hey,
hey, no snacking.
- [Narrator] But later
on it will be Andy's job
to teach the calf to drink
it's milk from a pail
and to eat other feed.
- [Crow] Hey, this is skim.
- [Narrator] Uncle
Jim and Bill make sure
the grown up cows
are properly fed.
That they get grain
and grass and silage.
All the good food and
clean water they need
to make good, fresh milk.
- [Mike] Well, you'll
pay one day, hayseed.
- [Tom] You'll get
what's coming, farmer.
- [Narrator] There was
plenty for everybody to do.
Betty helped Jane take
care of the baby lamb.
- [Crow] And prepare
a mint sauce.
- [Narrator] And they
learned about pigs, too.
- [Tom] More than
you'd ever wanna know.
(shouting)
Don't ever do that.
- [Crow] A very special
Zuckel family reunion.
So this is enough to get
you up in the morning, huh?
Okay, so, cities, nightclubs
don't mean anything to you.
- [Narrator] George
and Andy help Bill feed
the pigs every day.
- [Tom] Day after
life sucking day.
- [Narrator] While Betty and
Jane helped with the baby.
- [Tom] Drink it, just drink it!
- [Crow] These would
make nice purses.
- [Tom] Oh, the lunch counter
at Tom and Rosie's diner.
- [Narrator] Pigs don't
have good table manners
but they enjoy their dinner.
A mixture of milk
and ground grain.
Later they will eat corn
and other kinds of beef.
- [Crow] Oh yeah, and then
later they'll bring around
the desert tray.
- [Narrator] Baby chicks too--
- [Mike] Hey they're women, oh.
- [Narrator] Special mixture
of ground up grain, milk
and other feed.
This is Betty and
Jane's favorite chore.
The baby chicks are
so soft and cuddly.
- [Crow] And squishable.
- [Narrator] On
the farm a big dog
has plenty of room
to run and play
but he is more than a pet.
He also protects the family.
- [Tom] From rival farm gangs.
- [Narrator] But all
the puppies have to do
is eat and play and sleep.
- [Mike] Look at the puppy.
- [Crow] Oh one
foggy Christmas eve,
Santa came to say.
- [Narrator] Jane's kitten
loves to drink his milk.
- [Tom] But he wishes
he had a straw.
- [Narrator] And Jane
and Betty enjoy playing
with the kittens.
- [Crow] They enjoy
neutering them, also.
(bell ringing)
- [Narrator] When the
dinner bell rings no one
has to call the girls twice.
They run to the house
and wash up quickly
so they won't be late.
- [Tom] They have obsessive
compulsive behavior.
- [Narrator] Living on
a farm makes you hungry
and Aunt Helen is
certainly a good cook.
- [Mike] Given her limitations.
(light music)
- [Crow] Jerry Lee Lewis
joins the family for dinner.
(light music)
- [Mike] Ah yes, now's the time
for Uncle Jim's
fundamentalist dogma.
- [Tom] But I don't like food.
- [Narrator] Look at all
the wonderful things to eat.
- [Crow] At restaurants.
- [Narrator] It takes
all kinds of good food
to build up muscles and let
us grow bigger and stronger.
- [Mike] Mostly just butter.
- [Tom] Susie drains the
last of her dirty banana.
- [Crow] That's why
I'm burning my bra.
- [Mike] Repressed emotions help
the evening pass
without incident.
(light music)
- [Tom] Man your dad goes on.
- [Narrator] The children
are ready for bed
after a busy day on the farm.
- [Mike] Day one is
over at long last.
- [Tom] She's dreaming
of midtown Manhattan.
(rooster crowing)
- [Mike] Three hours
later, it's up again.
- [Crow] Back home
a Hershey's truck
has overturned and
everyone is getting all
the free chocolate they want.
- [Tom] Uncle Jim's
outta control.
We frag him today.
- [Narrator] This is
the way the summer went.
Play, work, and rest.
The children helped
with the chores.
- [Tom] Let my people go!
- [Narrator] While Bill
helped in the corn field.
- [Crow] Despair
was the bumper crop.
- [Narrator] Andy and George
kept the vegetable garden
clear of weeds.
- [Tom] I remember
ringing a bell.
- [Narrator] Jane and Betty
brought in fresh eggs each day.
- [Tom] Given by
disgruntled chickens.
- [Narrator] And helped Aunt
Helen with the house work.
- [Mike] I was rhubarb
queen of the five state area
in '48 so many gentleman
callers I had in my day.
- [Narrator] It was fun, too.
Especially riding the horses.
- [Crow] Why it's a
wonder cities even exist.
- [Narrator] Whenever
they were hungry
in the middle of the afternoon.
- [Tom] Too bad.
- [Narrator] There
were snacks under
the shady trees
and the big yard.
- [Mike] They had to graze
just like the animals.
- [Crow] Mm, pig's knuckles.
- [Tom] Uncle Jim's sick again.
Mm, good white hardy white
bread for white, white people.
- [Mike] Sis takes to the
comfort of cream items.
- [Narrator] And twice
a week letters from home
in the big mail box
beside the highway.
- [Tom] Thank you
for your request
to come pick you up, we
are sorry to inform you
that we cannot.
- [Narrator] As the
summer passed everything
seemed to grow.
The corn was knee high
on George when he came.
Now it's taller than he is.
- [Tom] George is
clearly shrinking.
- [Narrator] Andy's
calf is bigger
and eating like a grown cow.
- [Crow] With a knife and
fork like a real gentleman.
- [Narrator] The lambs
are almost grown.
And look how big
the pigs are now.
- [Tom] Equal rights for pigs!
- [Narrator] The little chicks
have become grown chicks.
- [Crow] They want to
wear makeup and nylons.
- [Narrator] George and
Betty have grown bigger
and stronger too.
George can even shimmy
up that rope now.
- [Tom] The stage
hand helps him too.
- [Narrator] Yes, they've
had a wonderful time.
They've learned how animals grow
through good nourishing food.
- [Crow] I think it's dead.
- [Narrator] They've
learned how work
and play and fun go
together on the farm.
- [Tom] Elsie and I are in
love and you can't stop us.
- [Narrator] They've
had good nourishing food
to grow on and plenty of sleep.
- [Tom] Why Uncle Jim's
even enrolled them
in the Posse Comitatus.
- [Crow] Ah, corn, coming
after me, stalks attacking me!
- [Tom] Shh, shh.
- [Narrator] The summer
is over and George
and Betty are waiting
for their parents
to take them back to the city.
- [Robots] Freedom!
- [Mike] Ebner, just throw
them their winter clothes
and then floor it.
- [Crow] Hey, they're
driving right by, wait, wait!
- [Narrator] It's
time for goodbye, now.
But the children will have a lot
to tell their friends at home.
- [Mike] Heck, I was
pretty hard on 'em Clark,
but I think you'll understand
when you see how well
behaved they are.
- [Narrator] It'll
be a long time before
either George and Betty.
- [Crow] Learn to forgive.
- [Narrator] Or
Andy and Jane forget
that summer of fun on
Uncle Jim's dairy farm.
- [Tom] You weren't there
when we had our summer of fun.
We went to a condo in Orlando.
- [Crow] Goodbye, we'll send
you that arm if we find it.
- [Mike] So long you
corn shucking suckers!
- [Tom] A Jam Handy, ha, ha!
(light music)
- [Tom] The story of
Wisconsin sausage.
- [Crow] You get your hand out
of that cookie jar, young man.
- [Mike] Oh he's so lucky,
he has those high cheekbones.
- [Crow] That's the
Edvard Munch painting
that wasn't stolen.
- [Tom] Looks like Ivan Lendel.
- [Crow] No, sorry, can't
work up any interest
in that group of people, sorry.
This isn't a very good
animation sequence.
- [Tom] You know, this is
exactly how Leakey found Lucy.
She was leaky.
- [Crow] This is the best Saul
Bass credit sequence ever.
- [Tom] You know, can't say
these people interest me either.
- [Crow] No, not a lick.
- [Mike] Well how about?
- [Tom] Nah.
- [Crow] No, not a lick.
- [Tom] Well the, no.
- [Crow] Come on, make
with the fright already.
- [Mike] Yeah, bring
on the scare, man.
- [Tom] The big Cunha, Cunha.
- [Mike] Cunha, Cunha
- [Crow] Oh yes, it's
Ralph, it's my picture
we do it my way Brooke.
- [Mike] All right
Brooke, Mr. Auteur,
let's see what you got.
- [Tom] Bring back the
skeleton skull guy.
- [Crow] They are so out
in the middle of the sea.
- [Mike] Fellas, it's
too rough to feed ya.
- Hey, Tony, watch it will ya?
We wanna get back to
port nice and dry.
- Yeah, you trying to
drown us or something?
- Don't worry, just don't worry.
- [Tom] The Exxon Valdez.
- I can navigate this
stuff with one hand.
- Oh Johnny, I think
he's at it again.
- [Mike] Yes, it's
the booze barge.
- [Tom] Save your ID,
you're a fine girl.
- [Crow] Stay right
there I wanna know
where you are at all times.
- If he does that once more
I think I'm gonna get sick.
- I think all this action
has made the fish sick.
I can't seem to make any
contact with 'em at all.
- [Mike] Shut up, wise.
- Okay Betty, let her go.
- [Crow] She's
tossing her panties.
- [Tom] Mm, that's
the last pair, honey.
- Not bad, not bad at all.
- Here, you wanna try it?
- Sure, only there's one hitch.
- What?
- No more bottles.
- [Mike] Well the
captain can rectify that.
- I guess we'll have to
play a different game.
- [Tom] Chutes and
ladders, heh heh.
- What can we do out here?
- Well this is always fun.
- [Crow] Looking at your roots.
(grunting)
Oh Audie I think you really
hurt something this time.
- Of all the girls
in the world I had
to get mixed up with the
daughter of a Judo expert.
- [Tom] Foreshadowing.
- Daddy told me lots
of men like to wrestle.
- Well, that's not exactly
what I had in mind.
- [Crow] I want you
to smash my face
into the side of ship.
- [Mike] I'm glad I
bought my Valero jacket.
- [Tom] How come
you don't Judo me?
- Hey come here, come here.
- What is it?
- [Crow] Water, lots of it.
- There's island way over there
that I don't remember
seeing before.
- [Mike] Yeah, large land
masses are easy to miss.
- Well this is the brightest
day we've had on our vacation.
Musta been hidden in the
mists out there before.
- Oh, a mysterious
hidden island.
Let's go ashore.
- [Tom] Let's go ashore.
- What for?
- Well, maybe we can find
some hidden pirate treasures.
- [Crow] In the gift shop.
- Maybe it would be fun.
Well, what'd ya say, Johnny?
- Oh why not?
This boat's costing us enough.
We might as well see
everything we can.
Hey Tony, put in here,
we wanna go ashore!
- [Mike] Can do!
- [Tom] Robert Maxwell,
the untold story.
- [Crow] I'll just run
up to the lido deck
and see what Issac is doing.
- [Tom] Well he's dead,
why didn't he just say so?
- Boy he's really
tied one on this time.
- Looks like he's gonna
be out for quite awhile.
- What are we gonna do?
- Well, I know I can get
this boat in close enough
to the island to
get anchor down.
But I'm not sure I can get
us back to the main island.
So I guess our little
treasure hunt's
the best thing to do until
our navigator sobers up.
- [Mike] I'll just keep
making wry comments.
- I'll take us in
closer to the shore.
- Okay.
- [Tom] What's a dingy?
- [Crow] Thank
you, please be sure
to fill out your comment cards.
- [Mike] Sure hope you
know how to fly this thing.
- [Crow] Okay, we detonate
at about 100 yards out.
- [Tom] Oh man, I went home
with this boat last night?
- [Mike] Ugh, time to
visit the poop deck
if you know what I mean, geez.
- [Tom] Wait, you forgot
Tallulah Bankhead!
- [Crow] Um, should we
have brought oars, or not?
- [Mike] I could quit anytime.
- Come back!
Come back, you fools!
Don't land there!
Come back!
- [Tom] The cruise
of wine and roses.
- [Crow] All right,
back to work.
(snoring)
- [Mike] Oh no, they
forgot the piano.
- [Crow] Tonight, love and
the landing at Normandy.
- Hey, I wonder if
anyone lives here.
- Oh, no chance.
If there'd have been any
natives on this island
they'd have spotted
the boat before now
been down here trying to sell
us hand painted coconuts.
- What do we do now?
- Well, my intuition tells me
that Captain Kidd buried
his loot over there.
- [Crow] In her bra?
- Hey, let's race up there.
Last one doesn't get
any of the jewels, huh?
- [Tom] Hey, counter worker
from Long John Silver's.
- [Mike] Go fish.
- [Crow] Shoot, I wanted to sell
them painted coconuts, arr.
- See what'd I tell ya. This
looks just like the remains
of Captain Morgan's flag ship.
- But back there you
said it was Captain Kidd.
- I did?
- [Tom] So you're saying
I'm not good in bed?
- One pirate's gold is
as good as another's.
- [Mike] Back pedaling.
- I think I found something.
- [Crow] Oh, my hand, sorry.
- Oh what is it?
Armor, pirate's armor?
- Well, let's just say it's
something the tide washed in.
- [Tom] Remember, I
know more than you do.
- I think you're just a little
too young to know about it.
- [Mike] Yeah, women know
nothing about underwear.
- Hey gang, come here.
- [Tom] I'm Robert Reed.
Found some turtle
eggs let's smash 'em.
- [Mike] The head, I think.
- Did you find
something, Johnny?
- You bet I did, look.
- [Tom] Linguini.
- Ew, what is it?
- It's some of the best
eating in these waters.
A lot of clams around here, too.
- I'm getting hungry.
Hey, let's have a clam bake.
- Right, let's have
it tropical style.
- Well how do you mean?
- Well look, Pete and I
will go into the jungle
and get some banana leaves.
- [Mike] In the back,
it's a Japanese sub.
Hey, Robert, Japanese sub.
- That's fine, all
except the last part.
- Huh?
- Where you go, we go, right?
- Right.
- We'll all go for the leaves
and then we'll all dig.
- Okay, okay.
Come on, let's go.
- [Crow] Unfortunately they
landed on Bikini Atoll in 1947.
- [Mike] The lure of
the clam bake proved
to be their undoing.
- [Tom] Great plan, look, can
we just go to Red Lobster?
- What is a jungle
without banana trees?
- [Crow] Uh, a forest.
- Hey wait a minute.
- [Crow] If you lived
here you'd home now, what?
- It's not too old, either. I
can still smell the tobacco.
- That means that
somebody does live here.
- Well, not necessarily.
Maybe somebody just went
exploring a couple days ago
and then sailed away.
- I don't know why
but I'm scared.
Let's go back to the boat.
- There's nothing
to be scared of.
- Oh no, it'll only
take a few minutes.
Then we'll be back at
the beach, come on.
- Come on.
- [Tom] It's few minutes and
we're not back at the beach!
- [Mike] On his resume
Robert Reed listed this
as "The Tempest."
- [Crow] Oh, she's a Breck girl.
- [Tom] Smells like James
Galway is bringing up the rear.
- Whoa!
- Johnny!
- [Mike] How long do
we bake the clams?
- Johnny!
- [Crow] Ah, just bury him.
- He looks hurt.
- All right, I'll
get some vines.
We can use them to pull him out.
- [Tom] Or hang myself.
- It was deliberately dug here.
- But who could have done it?
- Oh I don't know, but I do know
that as soon as we get
him up outta that whole
we're getting out of here.
Wait a minute, Pete.
I'll climb down.
We'll need you here
to pull him up.
- [Mike] Yeah, we'll need
your massive bulk up here.
- [Crow] A little peak
into their home life.
- [Tom] They should
just clam bake him.
- [Mike] Yeah.
- Okay, start pulling.
- [Tom] Speaking of pulling.
- [Crow] I'm here to tell
you about Mutual of Omaha.
- [Tom] Oh.
- Help them, quickly.
(electronic beeping)
- Wow, well seems
like a good idea
and hey, good look with
your vegetable stand.
I'm gonna go off and be
Kenny G so I'll see ya later.
- Well, mighty
neighborly of you, Mike.
Take her easy.
Not much traffic here today, eh?
I wonder if this was
the best location
for my produce stand.
Suppose not a lot of
people have cars here
on the satellite of love.
(car honking)
Whoa, hey sounds like I got me
a potential customer
coming down the road.
Yeah, of course
the only guy I know
who has a car
around these parts.
Oh no!
Jeez, next time buy something!
(light music)
(honking)
- Yes, I came here
shortly after the war.
- [Tom] What did you do?
- [Crow] You okay honey?
- [Mike] Guys.
- A world completely free from
any kind of outside pressure.
- But what do you do here?
- Yeah, how do you get any
kicks in a place like this?
- Kicks?
- [Tom] My kicks just keep
getting harder to find.
- I have some diversions.
- [Crow] Or perversions.
- I've developed a kind
of passion for hunting.
- [Mike] And fudge stripes.
- So that's it.
That's why the trap was.
- No, no, you're quite wrong.
You see this island
was once the stronghold
of some renegades
from the mainland.
There may be one or two of them
still lurking in the jungle.
But that must have
been their handy work.
- But all these different
animals, they can't be native
to this island.
- They weren't.
- [Mike] Ya idiot.
- But you must know what
money can accomplish.
It's quite simple to import
any kind of wild beast
from anywhere in the world.
- [Tom] An odd production
of "Blithe Spirit."
- Other men collect fame
and riches, I collect.
- [Crow] Beer cans.
- Trophies.
- [Mike] Thank you.
- Get out of my way.
- [Crow] Oh Oscar, Oscar, Oscar.
- I thought you had visitors, I.
- [Crow] Kitty.
- I hear these strange voices.
- [Tom] There's a two
drunk minimum in this film.
- Yes Dean, these young
people have stumbled
unto my retreat.
- [Mike] All eight of 'em?
- I see that you're
not feeling well again.
- That's right.
Maybe uh--
- [Crow] Hey buzz off, pal.
- Shouldn't bother
with introductions now.
I'll go back to my room.
- I think that would be best.
You can meet our
young friends later.
- [Tom] I threw up on
your water buffalo.
I hope that's okay.
- That's right.
- [Mike] Because you
never get a second chance
to make a first impression.
- Meet our young friend later.
- [Tom] Yes.
- Later.
- [Tom] Bye retired
grifter, I'm going to sleep.
- [Mike] He's an odd duck.
- Dean was once a
very brilliant man
but I keep him here with me
because I feel sorry for him
and he's an excellent
chess player.
- [Crow] And he looks
terrific in a gingham skirt.
- You'll all enjoy his
company when he's sober
and can get a
chance to know him.
- Well I'm sure
that's right sir,
but I don't think
we'll get the chance.
We have to leave now.
You see, our boat's
anchored off the island.
- I'm afraid that's quite
out of the question.
You'd never make it through
this animal infested
jungle tonight.
- But our boat, you
see the man who owns it
doesn't know we went ashore.
And he's sure to wake up.
- You can put your
minds at rest.
I have a very competent staff.
They'll take care of everything.
- [Mike] We'll leave a light on.
- Will you excuse me a moment?
I'll be right back.
- [Crow] I need to
check my script.
(smacking lips)
Good god look at
those people, mm.
- [Tom] Hey everybody, guess
who's in my living room.
Robert Reed.
- Johnny, Johnny
what are we gonna do?
This place gives me the creeps.
- Oh I don't know, I'd kinda
like to see what gives.
- Sure and what'd ya
thinks gonna happen
when Tony wakes up
and finds us gone?
I mean he'll head
straight back to port.
Maybe remember to
report us missing.
We're liable to be
stuck here for days.
- Don't worry about that.
Tony won't be going
anywhere without us.
- What'd you mean?
- [Mike] I don't
know what I mean.
- I mean, I made sure of
that before we left the boat
by taking the rotor.
He won't be able to start
the engine without us.
- Oh Pete, you're wonderful.
- Well that takes
care of the boat but.
- Hold it, he's coming back.
- [Tom] I just changed
out of my smoking jacket.
- [Crow] Don't even think it.
- [Mike] She's got a whole
lot of face going on.
- May I present my wife.
- [Robots] Sure!
- Sandra, Betty,
- [Tom] Bear.
- Jeanne, Johnny and Pete.
I was sure that you would want
to make them welcome
to our island.
- [Mike] Welcome
to death island.
- Naturally, I am
glad to see you.
- [Crow] Did you bring Paxel?
- Will you be
staying for awhile?
- [Tom] Yeah!
- Well you see Mrs. Balleau.
- Yes they will, my dear.
I think I've convinced
them of the foolishness
of trying to leave tonight.
- [Johnny] But we
don't want to impose.
- It's our pleasure.
- [Mike] We'll make a
meatloaf of some sort.
- Isn't it Sandra?
- Of course.
- [Crow] He's working the jaw.
- Now if you'll show the
girls the guest room.
- [Tom] And the guest
to the girls room.
- Yes, will you
come with me please?
- [Crow] And see what the boys
in the backroom will have.
- [Mike] It's Eva Braun's
bed and breakfast.
- [Crow] Say, where'd
you get the babes?
- I've made arrangements for you
to spend a comfortable night.
- [Tom] On me.
- We can discuss your
leaving in the morning.
- [Tom] Mr. Carlin.
- [Crow] Hey Hartley,
sorry I'm late, ya idiots.
- Prepared a room for you.
He will take you to it.
- Well I don't think we oughta--
- Goodnight.
- [Tom] Don't let
the bed bugs bite.
- Don't worry, everything
will be taken care of.
(crow cackling)
- [Tom] Oh, and he has
a tendency to fondle
so please be careful.
- [Crow] Want turn down service?
- [Mike] As for the
rest of you, oh.
- [Crow] Now for some
microwave french fries.
Well now how about me,
do I care for a drink.
Well I oughtn't but, well
I'll have what I'm having.
- [Mike] God, I love liquor.
I should gain weight so I can
handle more of this stuff.
- [Crow] White shoulders!
Later that same drink.
- [Tom] Wow, that
stuff really works.
- [Crow] Nom, there's gin
on the corner of your mouth.
Mm, oh I got it.
- [Tom] Your lips are like
a crisp, delicious bacon.
- Dean, we have to be careful.
He could walk in any minute.
And his spies are
all over the house.
- I know.
- [Crow] The lion
may be watching.
- I can't take much more
of this madness, Sandra.
I can't go on forever pretending
to be a useless drunk.
- [Mike] It was fun for awhile
but my liver keeps
shutting down.
- Tonight we've got
to try to escape.
We've got to try again.
- But how Dean, how?
- [Tom] Howdy how?
- He can never allow anyone
to leave this place alive.
And he has made sure
no one ever will.
- I know.
- [Crow] She's got more
face than she needs.
- And now with these kids here,
I think we've got a chance.
- What do you mean?
- I've worked it
all out in my mind.
- [Tom] Anyone seen
my A-deck, whoa.
- [Mike] I was just talking
to Misses Nipple, I mean.
- Now Sandra,
entertaining our guest?
- [Tom] That's a trick
question, isn't it?
He looks like an
Easter Island statue.
- You've recovered from
your indisposition, I see.
I'm glad.
- Thank you.
- I was just about to take
a turn around the grounds.
Wouldn't you two
like to join me?
We go out so seldom.
- [Crow] We got this
thing we should probably.
- I was about to go to my room.
- [Tom] My face needs a rest.
- Dean?
- No, no thank you.
- [Mike] I was about
to go to her room too.
- I think I'll turn in too.
- Then you won't
mind escorting Sandra
to her room, would you?
- [Tom] Oh ick, well all right.
- [Crow] Allow me to accompany
you to my pants, I mean room.
- Good night.
- [Mike] Oh how banal.
- Dean?
- [Tom] I wasn't
looking at her butt!
- I've worked out a
very satisfactory design
for living here.
I think you realize that.
I hope you also realize
that the presence
of those four young people
here changes nothing
as far as we're concerned.
- [Crow] And I'm
still Victor Buono.
- I've taken care of everything.
- [Mike] I don't think
he suspects a thing.
(door closing)
(light music)
- You don't think we're
dreaming do you, Betty?
- [Tom] It's Rob
and Laura's bedroom.
- No, this is no dream.
But I can't think of a
better explanation, either.
- [Mike] It's the boys from
the camp across the lake.
- [Tom] Oh this map, I
love to touch this map.
- Come in.
- Are you all right?
- So far we are but I
just can't understand
what's happening to us.
- Neither can I.
- That big guy that took
us to our room up the hall
wasn't very friendly.
- I've got a feeling
this isn't as friendly
a place as that Mr.
Balleau tries to make out.
- [Tom] Shut up.
- I still can't figure
out how he got here
on the island in
the first place.
- Well I figure this
house was first built
by one of those, you know,
crackpot millionaires
about 100 years ago.
When Balleau found out
about it he sorta moved in.
- You know that could be it.
He said he had a lot of money.
- But why, oh I still don't
know what's going on here.
- [Crow] Neither do we!
- Well it's a cinch
nobody's gonna tell us.
So we'll just have to
find out for ourselves.
- [Pete] Yeah, but how?
- Let's split up and
have a look around.
- [Tom] Yeah, but how?
- Oh I don't know.
I'm kinda scared.
- Well there's nothing
to be scared about.
I mean, I'll be with ya.
- [Mike] My point exactly.
- And Betty, you'll be with me.
Now listen, don't get into
anything you can't handle.
If you find out anything
head straight back here
and we'll do the same, okay?
- Yup.
- [Crow] See ya at the
office on Monday, then.
- [Tom] Okay, kids let's
go sell that band candy.
(humming)
- [Mike] Is it time
to report back yet?
- Okay, this is where we split.
Pete, you and
Jeanne go that way.
- Okay.
- [Crow] Robert Reed's part
makes it look like he has
a lid on his head.
- [Tom] I think she's shorter
than she was a minute ago.
- [Mike] Do you have a few
minutes to take a survey?
- I promise to
release you but only
if you swear not to cry out.
- [Crow] And quit
licking my hand.
- All right, go
back to your room.
We'll go with you.
We've got to talk to you.
- What's this all about?
- Please go back to your room.
We cannot talk here.
Please, there is
death all around us.
- [Tom] Well, you
could crack a window.
- Okay, Betty come on.
- Hurry.
- [Crow] They progressed
a full 10 feet
before being captured.
- [Mike] Careful, there's death
all around us in here too.
- [Tom] No, we don't have
money for other sets.
- Well?
- There's something
I wanna tell ya.
- [Tom] Radishes make me burp.
- Unless you do
exactly as I say,
you'll never get
off this island.
- [Mike] There,
I've said my piece.
- [Tom] Hm, it looks
like Liberace's in there.
- [Crow] Indiana nerd
and the temple of dork!
(light music)
- [Mike] Am I waiting okay
or should I, and wait,
how's this, I'm waiting.
(ominous music)
- [Robots] Surprise!
♪ Happy birthday to you♪
- [Crow] There's a whole
nother room in there.
- There's a stairway
there that leads down
into some kind of a tunnel.
- So?
- [Crow] Sue?
- Come on, let's
see where it goes.
- Please listen to him.
- [Crow] Awight, I'm wistening.
- And ourselves.
- I don't understand
any of this.
- Well I'll try and explain
it as quickly as I can.
- [Tom] What was there's this,
the wind began to
twitch and then.
- But they're not there.
- What?
- Well they're out in
the house somewhere.
They're trying to find
out what's going on.
Just as we were
when you stopped us.
- That's bad.
- Oh I'll go look for 'em.
- No, no, stay here.
- [Tom] One of the stupidest
hostages we've ever had here.
- Let's just pray that
they'll be all right.
- [Crow] This is where they
kneel down with Kissinger.
(light music)
- [Mike] What'd ya
know, a microbrewery.
Of course, I can't drink.
- [Crow] An entire cave
made out of garbage bags.
- [Mike] Are we
over investigating?
We need to ask ourselves that.
We should probably hide
under the bed instead.
- [Tom] You're
constantly clammy, Steve.
(screaming)
- [Mike] Cadavers for Algernon.
- [Crow] She's
finally the size five
she's always wanted to be.
- [Tom] Ow, ow, Susan you're
squeezing my booster shot.
- [Mike] Come on, it's just
a Jaycees Haunted House.
- [Crow] The wall is covered
with Issey Miyake clothing.
- [Mike] Steve Allen, PI.
(ominous music)
- [Tom] I know, we'll
throw Gatorade at 'em.
- [Mike] Okay Mr. Villashez.
Come along, we'll get you
back to your room here.
- [Crow] I wonder what he scores
on the Myers-Briggs inventory.
(ominous music)
- [Mike] Okay, I've decided
that phase B of our plan
involves a lot of hiding.
- [Crow] Hi.
- [Tom] Love this job,
I can dress how I want.
- [Mike] Gulp.
- [Crow] Huh, when did I
have teenagers installed?
- [Mike] Oh man, if
he had caught 'em
it woulda been really awkward
because they haven't
been introduced yet.
- [Crow] This would
be really suspenseful
but for the fact that it isn't.
Oh no, they've stumbled
unto another room!
- [Mike] Well, there's
that air hockey game
that we gave him
that he never uses
and the rowing machine.
- [Tom] Oh, it's their
cotton candy lab.
Well are we having
the clam bake or not?
- [Crow] Quick, into the vat.
- [Tom] Ah, he's
changing the kitty liter.
- [Crow] Mm, nice back porch.
Oh crap, apple.
Hi again.
- [Tom] Employees must wash
hands before leaving dungeon.
- [Crow] Claussen Kosher
ladies, never cooked.
Always crisp.
- [Tom] Uh, I gotta limit
myself to about three seconds
of looking at that.
- [Mike] Well, time to
rinse out my silk things.
- [Crow] Man, if it weren't
for my hobbies I'd go nuts.
- [Tom] He's gonna make
some of his famous toe jam.
(groaning)
- [Crow] That's just so wrong.
- [Tom] Sorry.
- [Mike] Oh it shrunk.
- [Crow] Went a little too
far with the derm abrasion.
- [Tom] I usually don't look
good in flesh tones, but.
- [Crow] He-he-he, that's funny.
- [Tom] Jackie Mason?
- [Crow] What are you
doing with my head?
This head should not be here
it should be on Broadway.
- [Mike] This is one of
Jeff Smith's weirder shows.
- [Crow] It's fun to
watch a craftsman at work.
- [Tom] There we go,
just a little more,
there one of my best ones
if I do say so myself.
(slurping)
- [Mike] Now be sure to save
the giblets for the cat.
Now Basques are one
of the finest people
and they do wonderful
things with organ meat.
- [Crow] Oh, this
is too fattening.
I'll get rid of it so
I won't be tempted.
- [Tom] Now to go
crunch some numbers.
- [Crow] Long before Peter
Billingsley there was this guy.
We are not staying for dinner.
- [Tom] Would you, I.
- [Crow] Try and get outta my--
- [Tom] I can't, I hear you.
- I can't believe it.
It's just too awful.
- [Tom] Poor Lonnie.
- Every word is
true, I swear it.
- You have to believe us.
- [Crow] Ty-D-Bol really works.
- Not a word about this.
- Somebody, give me a hand.
- [Mike] Bad news, the
kitchen's not up to code.
- Jeanne, oh!
- You'll never
believe what we saw.
- [Mike] Boiled heads?
- I don't believe it myself.
- We just heard about it.
I guess it's true then.
- If they told you about
an unbelievable nightmare
it's true all right.
- Then that settles it.
We've got to try to get
out of here tonight.
- Tonight?
- [Crow] Let's just see
how the skin turns out.
- Sandra and I have
been saying that
to each other every
night for the last year.
- Why haven't you ever tried?
- Never had the opportunity.
Balleau has always kept
us pretty well covered.
- What can we do?
- Well I have a plan that
I think will give us all
a good chance.
- [Tom] We all dress
like Shirley Valentine.
- You and Betty stay here
and watch after Jeanne
and be sure she's all right.
Johnny I want you
and Peter to meet me
in the trophy room
in a little while.
Oh it's all right.
We have the run of the house,
only be careful what you say.
- Yeah but what about Balleau?
- You don't have to worry about
him for a couple of hours.
- [Mike] Yeah, he's in the can.
- He's out in the jungle again.
After another trophy.
(light music)
- Yee haw, Cambot!
(funky music)
Now get in a line, get in a row,
grab your partner, here we go!
Swing her high
and swing her low.
Don't step on that
pretty little toe.
Now promenade.
Woo hoo, yee haw.
Eating turkey,
eating corn bread.
Jeans, skinny jeans
real well fed.
Allemande left and
allemande right.
Allemande left and allemande
right, now promenade.
Woo hoo.
- Yee haw!
- Woo hoo!
- Allemande right
and form a chain now,
form a star and
circulate to your left.
Ladies train now,
dosey doe allemande
and kick ball change
'em, now promenade.
Woo hoo, woo hoo!
Shake for breakfast,
shake for lunch,
a sensible meal
that you can munch!
Lowest prices all the time,
refreshing splash of lemon lime.
They closed the market,
the factories too.
Not just England it's
a cruel world, pretty.
Pretty like it, there's
no future, no future, ah!
(screaming)
Anarchy, anarchy!
Now promenade.
(klaxon alarm)
- Oh we got movie time, woo!
(funky music)
(electronic beeping)
- [Tom] Yee hoo!
- [Crow] Stop it, I'm
done with that game.
- Does he go out every night?
- Yes, every night
that he can hunt.
- [Tom] Wow, how
can he afford it?
- What, I mean who?
- Who, out there in that jungle
there are already several men
that he's driven insane.
- [Tom] With his low prices.
- And now there's
also, probably,
the owner of your boat.
- Tony?
- Well he must still
be out on the boat,
the engines won't work.
- No, well I'm sure that
by now Balleau's men
have taken that boat to the
other side of the island
to the hidden cove.
- Hidden cove,
well where's that?
- [Tom] I don't
know it's hidden!
- That's where your only
chance to escape lies.
- How do you mean?
- [Mike] Pause.
- There are several
boats moored off shore.
- [Mike] Pause.
- Someone will have to swim
out to one of them and.
- [Mike] Pause.
- Try to make it to the
mainland to get help.
- Well I'm not much of
a swimmer but I'll try.
- No, no.
- [Tom] You ain't
much of anything.
- I'll do that myself.
And Sandra will come with me.
- Sandra?
- That's right.
She's an excellent swimmer.
- [Tom] And a damn good cop.
- And even if we don't make it.
- [Crow] The Secretary
will disavow any knowledge
of our actions.
- Drowning would be
better than what Balleau
has in mind for both of us.
- [Mike] It'd just
be really bad.
It's alls that I'm saying.
- Now where do we
fit into all of this?
- [Tom] Where do we
- [Crow] Man his shirt is so
tight you can see his liver.
- You're gonna have
to cover for us.
If the guards find us gone
divert their attention
until we get to the boat.
And after that, well
after that I'm afraid
you'll have to look
out for yourselves
until I can come back with help.
- [Tom] Oh, fine, can
we end the scene please?
- Johnny?
- [Crow] What?
- I know it doesn't
sound very promising
but believe me it's the
only chance you've got.
- [Tom] What is?
- Well, I guess we'll
have to take it.
(exhaling)
- Good, now listen to me.
The first thing we do.
- [Mike] Let's kill
all the lawyers.
- Is go over to the north shore.
- [Crow] Arr, I dreamed
I went to Mandalay.
Arr, Jim boy.
- [Mike] Dating at the
College of St. Catherine.
- [Tom] That looks
like President Bush.
- [Crow] I tell ya,
honey, Barbara's got
eyes like an eagle.
- [Mike] Well I just had a wry
conversation, I'll tell ya.
- Did they get away?
- So far so good. I went as
far as the front door with 'em
and nobody saw me.
- Well those guards must
be getting careless.
One of 'em walked
right by Sandra's room
without checking it.
- Hold it.
- [Tom] Hi, we're
outta the sea bass.
Just thought I'd tell ya.
- [Mike] My name's Whistlin'
Pete if you need anything.
- Do you think he knows?
- I don't know but
Dean and Sandra
have had time to
get into the jungle.
- [Crow] You think
they'll bungle?
- Let's hope they
make it to the cove.
- [Tom] What, oh damn,
no lifeguard on duty.
- Do you think we're too softy.
- Now wait a minute,
I just wanna make
sure of the direction.
That guard won't
be back right away.
Yes, that's it.
- Dean.
- What is it?
I may never get a chance
to say this again.
- [Crow] Never wear a speedo.
- I love you with all my heart.
- [Crow] I hope
we'll boil together.
I wasn't finished.
- Darling, we won't fail.
We can't fail.
- [Mike] Ew, he's
unhinging his jaw.
- [Tom] I love to lamprey.
- Come on.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Well, time for
a little pole vaulting.
- [Mike] Well shouldn't
have stopped back there
this is a much
more dramatic shot.
- [Crow] Hey, he's
got an ugly stick.
- [Tom] The new Banana Republic
mature fit expands with you.
- [Mike] When are we
gonna have that clam bake!
- [Crow] Oo, that's cold.
- [Mike] Looks like my
grandma's house toward
the end of her life.
- [Tom] I splashed
some water on my pits.
- Did you find anything?
- No, I listened to
two guards talking.
One of them went
over to the cove
but he didn't mention
anything about the boats.
- It's been two days.
- [Crow] She grew!
- And no word.
- What I can't understand
is why we haven't heard
from Balleau before now.
- You don't think?
- [Mike] Yes, I do.
- I don't know what to think.
Hold it, somebody's coming.
- [Tom] Here's your
towels, Hartley.
- [Crow] Ah let's see,
which room had the rumaki?
- [Mike] Oh yeah, I knew
there had to be one of those.
- [Tom] Whacka, whacka, whacka.
- What's going on
in there, Johnny?
- Are you game to
try and find out?
- You don't mean.
- [Crow] Would you
finish your sentences!
- The answers to all our
questions lie behind that wall.
- [Mike] He shot the bear
in mid standing ovation.
- [Tom] I shouldn't let
Brian Epstein dress me.
- [Mike] The lion's
looking at me, Hartley.
- [Crow] Well you
don't think that.
You're not saying?
It's not true that.
- We're gonna find
out right now.
- [Tom] You know this
room could use more
of a hunting motif.
A gamey feel.
- [Tom] I wanna go see the
hall of record muskies.
- [Mike] Look at that up there,
it's a coelacanth on the wall.
(heavy breathing)
(dinging)
- [Crow] Please bear
with me folks, ha, ha.
Hey did you know in college
I was an Ursa Major.
I'm kidding!
(ominous music)
- [Balleau] Good evening.
- [Tom] Welcome to my
production of True.
- This is a pleasant surprise.
I wasn't expecting you
but I'm glad to see you.
Come in, come in won't you?
- [Tom] Don't step in the guano.
(squishing)
- I'd have something
I'd like to show you.
- [Tom] My mermaid outfit.
(screaming)
- [Crow] Mommy, mommy,
I'd walk a million miles.
- Welcome to my
private trophy room.
I had intended to
show it to you in time
but why not now?
- [Tom] During my
Montclare moment.
- [Crow] Now that one I like.
- [Below] That's Jacoby.
- [Tom] An eyeful.
He had strangled seven women
before he found his
way to my island.
- [Mike] We were
roommates for awhile.
- His experience made him an
adversary worthy of my skills.
- You mean you hunted
these people down?
And then killed them
and did that to them?
- [Crow] And
finished your degree?
- Exactly.
I hunted them and
shall I tell you why?
- [Tom] Oh cripes, yeah sure.
- I've been a
scholar all my life.
- [Mike] I've got a GED.
- I was curator of a large
museum when the war began.
- [Crow] The Roger Maris Museum.
- I, who had never killed
anything in my life,
found myself assigned
to duty as a sniper.
- [Tom] Hunker down.
- A sharp shooter because
of my steady hands
and keen eyesight.
- [Tom] 50 monologues
for male actors.
- It amuses me now that I
found it distasteful, at first.
- [Mike] Or is it
distasteful that I found out.
- As time went by I
adjusted to my new activity.
- [Crow] Uh, sir.
- What had been an unpleasant
duty became a pleasure.
Then it developed into a passion
and then into a lust.
- [Tom] And then
back into a pleasure.
- A lust for blood.
A lust that has
grown with the years
and one that I spend my entire
life with trying to satisfy.
- [Mike] Yeah, I like model
building a whole lot too.
- Don't be afraid.
I've merely preserved
my trophies as they were
at the moment of my triumph.
- [Crow] I wonder if he's
considered commemorative plates.
(girl screaming)
- [Tom] Okay, that pose
coulda been a lot worse.
- I see that my latest trophy
has really impressed you.
I'm glad, because I think
it's the best thing I've done.
So far.
- [Tom] And so
does Hilton Kramer.
- And because they
tried to betray me
it gave me great satisfaction.
- [Crow] Now, I think Salty
Ron has pecan ice cream for us.
- [Tom] Salty Ron.
- I must leave you now.
- [Mike] Am I being fay enough?
- Since you had no difficulty
finding your way here
I'm sure that when Miss Scott
has regained her composure
you'll be able to
see her to her room.
Oh yes.
- [Tom] I have another cliche.
- Just one thing more I'd like
to have you see before you go.
- [Mike] It's called Captain EO.
- [Crow] Exhibit under repair.
- You'll notice that this
niche has room for three.
Or even four.
- [Tom] If you
squeeze 'em a little.
- Trophies.
- [Tom] It's a little pricey,
but I think it's worth it.
- Tony!
- [Crow] Is this
your drunk, Hartley?
- Yes, Tony.
- [Mike] Tony, Tony, Tony, Tony.
- I think it only fair
that we should be here
at this time because
he's going to take part
in the game, too.
- No, no, please don't send
me out there with them.
- [Tom] Oh, I can't
stay cool anymore.
This is gonna be so fun!
- I paid you well to provide
me with subjects in the past.
I've warned you not to use
your boat for other purposes.
- [Crow] You went inner
tubing, didn't you?
- Allow these young people
to find their way here
without my knowledge,
I think it only right
that you should
share their fate.
- Do you mean?
- [Mike] Stop it!
- That's exactly what I mean.
Tony was my source of
supply for subjects.
In the past they were
always convicts escaped
from the penal island.
- [Tom] Te-hee, te-hee.
- [Crow] Stop it.
- I find him no
longer dependable.
- You really think you can
get away with this madness?
- Madness?
What I plan is a pleasant
evening's diversion.
- See I knew he was only
kidding. Well that's just a toy.
That couldn't kill anyone.
- [Tom] You're forgetting about
the boiled heads, aren't ya?
- [Mike] Is that Alf
on the wall back there?
- [Tom] I hope so.
- [Crow] Somebody took my bones.
- [Tom] It amuses me
and is also distasteful
that you think that I would.
(shattering)
- [Mike] Did I hit him, or?
- [Crow] Huh.
- [Tom] Well, that threw
cold water on everything.
- I guess it could
kill somebody.
- Yes, it can.
- [Mike] Now go
change your pants.
- And soon we'll
try to prove it.
- Please Mr. Balleau,
don't do this awful thing.
- Oh please.
- You have nothing to be
alarmed about young lady.
You're in no danger,
either of you.
Your life here with me
will be a pleasant one.
You'll find me a most
accommodating host.
- Do you think Jeanne
and I will have anything
to do with you if you
sent Pete and Johnny out
and kill them in that jungle?
- Yes, I think so.
I know so.
No one has ever left this
island, dead or alive.
And since the unfortunate
incident involving
my wife has left me
without feminine company.
- [Crow] Except
for Minnie Pearl.
- Getting to know you
both better, much better.
- [Tom] Boy he bounces back
from a bad relationship.
- So it's not enough that you
have to make sitting ducks
out of Pete and me, you
have to hurt the girls too?
- Hurt them?
- Johnny, he really means it.
What are we gonna do?
- [Tom] Oh, how'd
that get there?
- I think you've
asked the wrong person
about your future activity.
Go with Jondor.
Jondor lock them in their room
and then come back at once.
- [Mike] His real
name's Clint but Jondor
has a certain ring.
- [Crow] It does.
Well, he's kinda cute, I guess.
I can change him.
(ominous music)
- [Mike] All right, mad men.
- Very touching, but to
return to your question, Pete.
- [Crow] The Mugwumps way.
- Up to a certain point. The
rest then will be up to you.
Are you listening to this, Tony?
It applies to you, too.
- [Mike] Yup, okay.
- Moonlight's bright
tonight so you will make
your way to the starting
point of the chase.
It's in the center
of the jungle.
Ivor will give you
exact directions.
- [Tom] Eyeball?
- The natives used to
call it the Tree of Death.
- [Crow] I call it Bernie.
- I will give you plenty
of time to plan your flight
before I follow with the cross
bow and just three of these.
Just three shots, that's
all I allow myself.
- [Tom] Or else I get silly.
- That's sporting
don't you think?
- [Crow] Ah, Eyeball.
- [Tom] It's Jondor, sir.
- You haven't answered me.
Don't you think it's
very sporting of me
to allow myself just one
chance at each of you?
- Oh sure, really sporting.
- [Tom] Frankly, I'm steamed.
- Marcus of Queensbury.
- And a jungle like
the palm of your hand.
With that thing that could
knock an elephant over.
You're gonna hunt us
down but we have nothing
to defend ourselves with.
- Not so fast, not so fast.
You haven't allowed me to finish
the entire plan of the
evening's entertainment.
- [Crow] There will
be a light deck lunch.
- Tony, here catch.
- [Mike] Where do you
drink outta this thing?
- Oh Tony, it isn't loaded.
- [Crow] Neither am I,
oh please just a taste.
- He had us alone in here
with an unloaded gun.
- It's time to start.
The odds are not
completely one sided.
Your youth and numbers against
my skill and experience.
You'll find the ammunition
in the branches of
the tree of death.
When that gun is loaded, my
life will also be subject
to how the hunt goes.
- [Tom] Tonight on
the Hollywood Palace.
- [Mike] Oh, oh real good plan.
Let's go to the Tree
of Death right away.
Maybe there's a map
that tells us the way
to the Tree of Death.
- [Crow] Let's visit
Mr. Owl, hoo hoo.
- [Mike] Tree of novelty items.
- Here it is, I found it.
- [Crow] It's Meow Meow Kitty.
Meow, meow, meow.
- Why that rat.
That lousy stinking rat.
- [Tom] Let's not call names
it'll escalate in to bitterness.
- He left only one shell.
- Because that's way
his twisted mind works.
- [Tom] I don't
like the villain.
- What'd ya mean?
- Don't ya see?
He allows himself three
shots, one for each of us.
And we get one shot at him.
- [Mike] I'm just about fed up.
- Well there's nothing
we can do about it.
Come on, give me the gun
and let's get moving.
- Oh no you don't, buster.
You just hand over that bullet.
- Don't be a fool, Tony.
I'm a better shot than you are.
- Yeah?
- [Tom] Are you
saying I'm a drunk?
- Have you ever shot a man?
- [Crow] Well I slapped
Andy Davis once.
- No.
- Well I have.
And I ain't taking any
chances no amateur.
- [Crow] (imitates
gunshot) whoops.
Are you done?
- Well which way should we go?
- I don't know which way
you two guys are going
but I'm going alone.
So long, suckers.
- Hey.
- [Tom] Well now
that was really rude.
- Hey come back here!
- No, no let him go.
- [Crow] I liked him.
- It's better if we do split up.
It doubles our chances.
- How?
- Well Balleau can't hunt
in two directions at once.
Now look, the way I figure
it, we must be right
about in the middle
of the island.
If we were to head that way,
try to get to the beach,
and then work our way
back to the house.
- Back to the
house, are ya nuts?
- [Mike] Well, I've got
a slight dementia but.
- Well let's try
to find the boat.
- No, we've gotta try and
get the girls out first.
- But Balleau said
he won't touch them.
- Never mind what he said,
I know what he meant.
- [Crow] Filthy
un-Christian sex.
- Come on, let's get started.
- I just don't see
how you figure--
- Nevermind, we've
gotta do what we can
and that's the first thing.
- [Mike] They found the tree
of interminable dialogue.
- Well here's hoping we
find the second thing
whatever that'll be.
- [Tom] I heard that.
- [Mike] I'm almost
ready mad doctor, dear.
Just freshening up.
- The guard's still out there
and wide awake.
- [Crow] And cute.
- Betty what are we gonna do?
Even if we do get
outta this room
where are we gonna go?
- I don't know.
- [Tom] We could
have a slumber party.
- Maybe we could find the boys
and try to get to the boat.
- We don't even
know where it is.
Oh, it's just no use.
♪ Where is love♪
- [Mike] Am I thinking
what I'm thinking?
- [Crow] Use your weighty hulk.
- Oh, even this
window is locked.
- [Crow] Oh, even the
spittoon is locked.
I could make placements
for the children.
- Come here, Jeanne.
- [Tom] Come on, move
it, move it, move it!
- Listen to me, I got an idea.
Don't ask any questions,
just do exactly as I say.
- All right, what do
you want me to do.
- Here.
- Oh.
- [Tom] I'm blind Tom, yar.
(shattering)
- [Crow] Just set that anywhere.
- Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
- [Tom] Not the Ming spittoon.
- I was moving it
and it just broke.
I'm sure I can fix it if
you could get me some glue.
- [Mike] Oh, this is
their cutest plan yet.
- I didn't mean to break it, it.
- [Tom] It broke.
- It was such a pretty vase.
(cackling)
- [Crow] Damn you all to hell!
- [Mike] New stuff killed.
- Jeanne come on, hurry.
- [Tom] But we need
to fix the vase.
- Come on, I'll
help you climb out.
- Out there?
But we'll be killed.
- No we won't.
There's a ledge out there.
We can work along that until
we come to an open window.
- What if there's something--
- Never mind, it's the only way.
Come on, hurry up.
Be careful, too.
- [Crow] Now, fly monkey's fly.
(humming)
(light music)
- [Crow] Action foliage.
- [Tom] Jondor, heel.
Now I got a head boiling,
I should be getting back.
- [Crow] You know, chopping
your own Christmas tree
is harder than you'd think.
- [Mike] When did he get nude?
God, I admire his jacket.
- [Crow] Brian Benben!
- [Tom] Man is he Flemish.
I wove you this mwuch.
- So Tony, we come to
the end of the trail.
- [Tom] The soul trail.
- [Crow] No, no,
it's broken, honey.
- I'm disappointed in you, Tony.
You've known me long
enough to realize
that I wouldn't give you a gun
without first taking the
precaution of removing
the firing pin.
- [Crow] And the
distributor cap.
- You find that hard to believe.
Well you see, Tony.
If I hadn't given
you the gun you would
have never given me the pleasure
of seeing your face at
the moment of the kill.
- [Tom] Oh wait,
it's not a pleasure.
- Oh no, please, please
don't do it, please.
I'll never give
your secret away.
I promise.
I'll get you more convicts!
- [Crow] I'll be
your best friend.
- I'll never make a
mistake again, please.
- [Crow] I got candy
bars in my room.
- All right Tony,
I'll reconsider.
- [Tom] But I already
have a best friend, bye.
- Oh thank you.
- [Crow] May I borrow
a shirt, by the way.
- You won't be sorry.
- Enough of this,
I have work to do.
You get back to the house.
Yes sir, yes sir
I'll go right now.
- [Crow] I'll make
you so proud of me.
- Tony!
- [Tom] I lied.
- I have reconsidered.
- [Mike] John Steinbeck
in of Mice and Murder.
(screaming)
- [Tom] Rail, rail against
the dying of the, ugh.
- [Crow] Oh, that
was a good one.
- I'm sure I heard a scream.
- [Mike] Well that
figures, boy am I cheesed.
- I can't tell.
I think it might just
have been a jungle bird.
- No I'm sure it was Tony.
That means we're next.
Come on, Johnny let's
try and find that boat
it's our only chance.
- Now we're not gonna
do anything until
we get the girls free.
Now come on.
- [Tom] The war's this way.
(chirping)
- [Crow] What are you doing,
no I don't want your filth.
- Hurry, back to
the Tree of Death.
We'll pick up the
other trail there.
- [Crow] It would be
ironic if the Tree
of Death ever got
Dutch elm disease.
- [Tom] Yeah, stuff of
death wouldn't be the same.
- [Crow] No.
- [Mike] Ah-ha, we're
back to our room, see.
- [Tom] Oh, it's like Cagney
and Lacey the attractive years.
- [Mike] Snoop Sisters,
the early days.
- [Crow] Where angels
go, trouble follows.
- Well we made it this far.
- Yeah, but where is this far?
- I don't know but
it's closer to far away
than back in that room.
- [Tom] You're deep.
- Come on.
- [Crow] Let's do the whole
thing over again, it was fun.
- [Mike] I just wanna
see the boiled heads.
It would be too bad
to come all the way
to this island and not
see the boiled heads.
- [Crow] Betty, my pants
have reached a crisis point.
- [Tom] Come on, we have to
find the secret to Bock Beer.
- Oh no.
That's the door to that terrible
work room I told you about.
- Oh.
- [Crow] Mine papa.
- Wait a minute.
Maybe we can find a knife
or something in there.
- [Mike] Then we
can bone some ham.
- Come on.
- [Crow] Oo, I'll go first.
- [Tom] Well you've
met the heads.
- [Mike] You know they
could wear the heads
and then escape as someone else.
- Over here.
- [Crow] You've
gotta believe me.
There were heads
all over the place.
- [Tom] Hey, booyah's done.
- We've gotta get
a couple of these
that we can carry easily.
- Oh it's no use, Betty.
Even if we did I
couldn't use one anyway.
- Oh Jeanne listen to me.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Nobody expects
the Spanish Inquisition
amongst our weaponry.
- Good evening, ladies.
- [Tom] I'm Peg Leg Dick.
- Keep away from us.
- [Crow] So you want hush
puppies or rice pilaf
with your lobster?
- I'm warning you, I'll use
this. Jeanne run for the door.
He can only get one of us.
- Mr. Balleau told me to
take good care of you ladies.
- Don't come any closer!
- Can't you see I'm harmless.
- [Tom] Isn't
everyone here phony?
- I'm not going to hurt you.
(screaming)
- [Mike] Uh, this doesn't
involve you, Betty.
(chuckling)
- Can't you see, can't you see?
- [Crow] Bob Packwood
goes a courting.
So you maybe wanna go out
and have coffee some time or?
(screaming)
- [Mike] Okay, half
off the soup today.
(screaming)
- [Crow] Ricky!
- [Tom] Jeez, he
looks younger already.
(smacking lips)
- [Mike] Wait, I still
haven't seen the heads.
- [Crow] That was
fun, who's next?
- [Mike] Pa!
- [Crow] I think I remember
one of the girls say
that if we were ever capture by
an evil hunter to go
ahead without 'em, okay?
- We're lost, what's the use?
It's only a matter
of time before
Balleau catches up with us.
- I don't think we are lost.
- The jungle's thinning out.
We must be getting
closer to the beach.
- [Crow] I think that
still qualifies as lost.
- So what?
I don't mean to put
you down, Johnny
but even if--
- [Tom] But you suck.
- Do find the beach,
then what are we gonna--
- Hold it.
- [Mike] Hey Jondor has
my latest Ted Nugent
bow hunting magazine come yet?
- Well come on, we
gotta make time.
- [Crow] Be gentle, uh, oh.
- This way.
- [Tom] He's in a
scene with Robert Reed
and he's the weeny.
(screaming)
- [Mike] Well someone's
got allergies.
- Don't make a sound.
(man screaming)
- [Tom] Look, John the Baptist.
- He hasn't seen us yet.
Back off.
- [Crow] I think
it's Charlie Callas.
(screaming)
- [Tom] Could I just
get some service!
(dramatic music)
- I can't get out.
- [Tom] Hi, can I help
ya. Oh I mean (screaming).
- I'm sinking.
It's quick sand.
- Don't struggle.
Keep quiet.
- [Crow] Come on, play Old
Testament prophet with me, ah!
- [Tom] Later, later.
(heavy breathing)
- [Mike] No, my muffins!
- Something scared him.
Look we gotta get
outta here, too.
- [Mike] Next year let's
just go to Branson, Missouri.
- I can't, I can't
make it, John.
I just can't make it.
- [Crow] Okay, see ya.
- [Tom] Here, I want
you to have this shirt.
- [Mike] Hey, I'm missing
one of my leeches.
- Get 'em off!
- [Crow] You take some off
too. I'll meet ya halfway.
- [Tom] The night they
invented champagne.
(inhaling)
- [Mike] I think we found the
weak link in the security.
(chuckling)
- [Crow] That's the
one, he's the cute one.
(electronic beeping)
- Ah, hello.
Welcome to tonight's
mystery murder dinner party.
- I did it!
- Crow!
Jeez, you ruined everything.
- Oh, for crying out loud.
- I had this whole colonel thing
worked up and then, ah god.
- [Mike] I don't believe it.
(sniffing)
- Oh, hey is this
whole pie for me?
Oops.
(light music)
Oh yeah, turns out
Rosebud was his sled.
Yeah, and then "Crying
Game" well chick had a--
- [Together] Hey, hey, that's.
- Do you think you can make it?
- Do I gotta choice?
- [Mike] Boy, I
feel really good.
I think I needed
that bloodletting.
- [Crow] Sure you don't wanna
check my butt for leeches?
- [Tom] Yes, I'm sure.
- [Mike] I'm gonna get a
rash from my wet pants.
- [Crow] Ah, take that.
- [Tom] Chivalry in
case a woman comes by.
- [Crow] The defiant debs.
- Oh!
- [Crow] Oh.
- Are you hurt?
- No, just my dignity.
- [Tom] Oh, and my
ankle's shattered.
- Now what?
- Well we're out of
that awful house.
Now we'll have to
try to find the boys.
- I just hope Balleau
doesn't find them first.
- [Mike] Oh this is
"The Osterman Weekend."
- [Crow] Oh, ah, you,
oh look at this, oh, ah,
the castle's this
way, come with me.
Oh daddy keeps his porno.
- Twice tonight you've
given our position away
and now you can't
even find the trail.
- [Tom] Well boss, you see I
got this pinched sciatic nerve.
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] Ha, cold, oh cold.
- Be grateful that
your own stupidity
will save me the trouble
of getting rid of you.
- [Crow] If I could
just voice an objection.
- Too sad the leeches will
do their work so well.
You might have made an
interesting specimen
for my museum.
(screaming)
- [Tom] Ah, that's my ride.
- Oh I'm sorry, Jondor.
- [Crow] Oh you are not.
- I won't be able to stay
to enjoy your last moments
but I am urgently
required elsewhere.
- [Mike] But where are the
blank checks, by the way?
Well, I'll find 'em.
- [Tom] Visit the
La Brea Tar Pits.
(dramatic music)
- Okay.
- [Crow] It's all right.
- I guess so.
- We better keep moving then.
We'll never find the
boys just sitting here.
- May I say it just
once more, please.
- What?
- [Tom] Member.
- I'm scared.
- Well if it makes you
feel any better, so am I.
But we've got to go on.
- [Tom] Just tuck the
bone back under the skin.
- Let's go.
- [Mike] Seems like
you need a pants horn
to get into those things.
(screaming)
- Ah, ah, ah!
- [Crow] Choo!
(girls screaming)
- That's Betty.
- And Jeanne.
- Come on.
- [Tom] And weird guy.
- [Mike] Uh, let me
baptize you just once.
(girls screaming)
- [Crow] How about
next Wednesday then?
- [Mike] This guy always
sits next to me on the bus.
(man screaming)
- [Tom] It amuses me that
someone is chewing the scenery.
(man shouting)
- [Crow] Your island
is really very, oh!
- [Tom] He culls the
weak from the herd.
Robert Reed is Buford T. Pusser.
- [Crow] In Prancing Tall.
- Are you all right?
- [Mike] Have we had
the clam bake yet?
- Come on, let's
get outta here fast.
- [Tom] I wish they'd
invent computers
so I'd have somewhere to belong.
- [Crow] Well this
movie's back on track.
(groaning)
- [Tom] Well, back at it.
I think it's the
others who are crazy.
- [Crow] Oh I blew it. I
should've said, ew, eh.
Ew instead of eh.
- So it's you.
- [Mike] You're looking well.
- I had thought to permit you
to enjoy the
hospitality of my island
while I took care of
more pressing business.
- [Tom] Can I get a
grunt in here edgewise?
- [Crow] I'd rather
die than have to listen
to that guy talk.
(man screaming)
- [Mike] It kinda hurts.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Ah, so it's you.
- [Crow] Reduce, recycle, reuse.
- [Mike] You know, older men
always carry handkerchiefs.
- [Tom] And this is why.
- [Crow] I'm kind of
anal about this stuff.
- [Mike] Okay, call me if
there's any pain or discomfort.
- [Tom] Been good
talking to ya, so long.
- [Crow] You know
he may be in danger
of over harvesting the
game on this island.
- [Mike] I think
they're letting us in
on details we really
don't need to know.
- [Tom] The Kraut
is a lonely hunter.
- [Crow] I should just
put in some strip malls
and be done with it.
- [Mike] Really not a
lot to do on this island.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Looks like a
really uncomfortable crotch.
- I don't know how
long we can hold onto
this kind of luck.
- If Balleau doesn't
get us the strain will.
- We're gonna have to try
a real grand stand play.
(humming)
- From the sound they made,
I'd say the whole bunch
is out looking for us.
- Good, at least they'll
be outta the house.
- Pete drop down and see if
you can see any signs of him.
- [Crow] Well why
don't you drop down
and kiss my pink behind, well.
- Be careful.
- [Crow] I want you the be
alive when I break up with you.
- Let me at 'em.
- [Tom] Damn the
torpedoes, please.
- [Crow] Okay, dropping down
oh, oh, I could hurt my ankle.
I just have to drop and then.
- It's okay, it's okay, come on.
- [Crow] He's a
regular Sacagawea.
- [Tom] I jumped
down and scouted
the place out like
you said, I did!
- Look, we haven't got
a chance without a gun.
We've got to get back
into the trophy room.
- We can't, we just
got outta there.
- That's just why we can take
a chance on going back there.
Balleau's guards will still
be out looking for you girls.
Now if we can shake Balleau
and get back there
before the guards do,
we can get the guns and maybe
have a chance to stay alive
long enough to find
the boat, come on.
- [Mike] You see
me scouting, honey?
I scouted.
(light music)
- [Crow] I haven't seen a
coworker for weeks, oh well.
- [Tom] I will not
let down my vigil.
- That's one guy that's not
out combing the bushes for us.
- Should we jump him, Johnny?
- No, I don't think so.
I think our best chance
is to try and sneak past him.
- [Crow] I gots one job
but I does it well, arr.
And I hates Robert Reed.
- [Tom] Hey mister,
can we go in now?
(giggling)
- [Crow] Maybe I
can kill a bush.
Ah, it wouldn't be the same.
- [Tom] I suppose I
shoulda kept my town house
in Manhattan, well.
- [Mike] Ah, time for my story.
- [Crow] I wonder if there's any
of that German potato
salad left in the fridge.
♪ Deutschland,
Deutschland, uber alles♪
(dramatic music)
- [Mike] It's just
as I remember it.
- [Crow] Are you
guys ready for this?
Remote control everything.
- It's locked.
- Are you surprised?
- Oh very funny.
Don't just stand there.
Try and find something
to open it with.
- [Tom] This would be the kind
of blood hunt I get in on.
- Well if we get it,
what are we gonna do?
- We're gonna try
and get outta here
and find the boat.
- Oh thank goodness.
I don't wanna stay in here
any longer than we have to.
- Yeah, yeah, that
oughta do the trick.
- [Tom] That was almost as hard
as the time that
I went scouting.
- [Crow] Shut up.
(light music)
Get all the way out there
and my laxative kicks in.
- [Tom] All quiet sir.
- Neck broke.
- [Mike] You get what
you pay for, I guess.
- [Crow] No wait, I think I have
a neck in here
somewhere, ah yes.
- [Mike] Had a great job
as an actuary downtown
but no, gotta come
out and buy an island.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Well look at this
Lucas McCain's armoire.
- [Crow] I'm the NRA.
- There's no ammo here.
- Well there's gotta be.
These guns are useless
to us without it.
- I know, I know.
- Somebody's coming.
- Let's get outta here.
- [Mike] "Scooby Doo"
the motion picture.
- [Tom] Shh, I
can't stop laughing.
(cackling)
- [Crow] He should be thankful
for his smoking jacket
or else he'd be walking
around in his underwear.
- [Mike] I think I'll settle
in with some erma Bombay.
- [Tom] Maybe a little
schnitzel bonk for dinner.
- [Crow] I hope I
didn't kill the cook.
(ominous music)
- [Mike] This guy looks like
a sockeye salmon about to spawn.
- [Tom] Ack, those
darn Mendez boys.
- [Crow] Oh good, my
lingerie is still here.
- [Mike] I feel so violated.
- [Tom] Manos.
- [Crow] I wish the bear
would put on some pants.
- [Tom] No cookies, not
now, not ever, never!
(light music)
- [Tom] You know, I
could sublet this.
- [Mike] Maybe I do have
room for a pool table.
♪ But a cave is not a home♪
- [Crow] This is the biggest
bathroom I've ever seen.
- [Mike] Ladies and
gentlemen, Spalding Gray.
- [Balleau] Well
then, I'm flattered
that someone should
want to further look
at my little souvenirs.
No one else has ever
come back a second time.
- [Tom] Maybe I'm over charging.
- [Balleau] Alive.
- [Mike] Hello?
- It's rather dark in here.
Perhaps we should have
a little more light.
- [Crow] Clap on.
Mammy, sir.
- Well, let's try else where.
- [Tom] He's regained
his sang foud.
- Or there.
- [Crow] Does he even take
'em out and play with 'em?
- Well, well.
- [Mike] Just switch 'em on
all at once you show off.
- Or there I imagine.
- [Tom] Yes, I call
that one Lutheran Love.
- There's plenty of time.
- [Crow] I've got fudge.
- It's strange about
these old walls.
- [Tom] Yeah, what's that?
- The smallest
sound is amplified.
If one sits quite
still one can hear
the slightest murmur.
- [Tom] Murmur.
- [Mike] Murmur, murmur, murmur.
- Sometimes even the
slightest breath.
- [Crow] Really?
- [Tom] See, I'm suggesting
that there may be
someone in here.
- A certain closeness
about this place.
I've never corrected it.
It helps preserve my trophies.
- [Mike] Maybe when I retire.
- But at times it does
make breathing difficult.
- [Crow] He does
this twice a day
and once in awhile he
actually finds somebody.
- I've sat here so long that
I find I can sit for hours
and not make a single sound.
- [Mike] Why don't
you demonstrate?
(chortle)
- Not a single sound.
(coughing)
- [Tom] I got you, I
got you, I got you!
- A single sound.
- [Mike] Not a single sound.
- [Tom] Single sound.
- Stay just where you are.
- [Crow] You guys are
pathetic, look at you.
- That's far enough fellow,
don't come any closer.
- I think it was rather rude
of you to force
open my gun cabinet.
But I'll overlook it since you
spared my ammunition chest.
- [Mike] Pete, Pete, poker face.
- Oh yes, I know your
guns are quite useless.
No, no.
- [Tom] Fix bayonets!
- I wouldn't try
that if I were you.
- It would only
hasten your death
and that of all of your friends.
- Okay, Balleau.
You win.
- I never doubted it, did you?
- Well, why don't
you get it over with?
- Oh, not so fast
my young friend.
I have an idea
that appeals to me.
- [Crow] Chic peas.
- Let me group you
in this setting alive
as you will be in
death, for all time.
- [Mike] Well, okay.
- What do you mean?
- I'll show you, my dear.
I've never had the pleasure
of a trial arrangement
of my trophies.
You, Pete, over there.
- [Tom] Link, Julie, over there.
- Move!
- [Crow] Look over your
shoulder and wet your lips.
- And you my dear, I think
you'd look most effective
with your arms
around Johnny's neck.
- Now wait a minute.
You promised to
let the girls live.
- That's right, I did promise.
But since they obviously
helped you kill the guard
I'm afraid I can no
longer trust them.
- Guard, we didn't
kill any guard.
- [Mike] We didn't
steal no bike, neither.
- Honest, the only guard
we saw was at the gate
and we sneaked past him.
- [Crow] Snuck.
- Quiet, don't make a sound.
Any of you, not a sound.
- [Tom] Shoulda had a tech
rehearsal, I had to, ah.
- You, over to my chair.
And throw the last switch.
Move, quickly, quickly.
- [Mike] Finally
Pete's the AV geek
he's always wanted to be.
- [Balleau] Hurry,
the last switch.
- [Crow] Um, is that
the red one, sir?
There are two here.
Which one is the last one?
- [Tom] Huh, David Letterman.
- [Crow] Hey.
- [Mike] You got any salt, I
got a couple of hangers here.
- Jondor, stop.
- [Crow] No leeches
in the house.
- I warn you.
- [Tom] It's the blue switch,
here let me get it for you.
(gunshots)
- [Crow] Let's go hide
in the head boiling room.
(growling)
Oh, ow.
- [Tom] You see when lackey's
turn on their masters
they become bullet proof.
(screaming)
- [Crow] Hey buddy
I love ya, come on.
(screaming)
- [Crow] Yow, that hurts.
- [Tom] So why this symbolism?
Did Christ hunt people
on deserted islands?
- [Mike] The Johnson
coat rack company
issued a recall today.
- Take it easy Betty.
It's all over and
we'll be safe now.
- [Crow] We're free to be wry.
- But we're not off this
horrible island yet.
Those others.
- Don't worry about them.
Now that Balleau's
dead I don't think
that they'll give
us any trouble.
- [Tom] He's been so right
about everything so far.
- I guess Balleau
never thought he'd be
the prize exhibit
in his own museum.
- [Tom] Guess not.
- [Mike] You know if
earlier he had said,
I'll never been
impaled on my own rack
this would have been ironic but.
(man screaming)
(electronic beeping)
(screaming)
- Wow, you scared me.
- What the heck are you?
- Look, as long as
Nelson's on the loose you
and I are not safe.
Now keep low and stick with me.
- What?
- Tom, Mike's secretly
been hunting us down.
Think about it.
He's just like the
guy in the movie.
All alone, isolated.
- Yeah.
- Was a sniper during the war.
- He was?
- Well I'm pretty sure, yeah.
- Crow, you don't think?
- Hi guys.
(screaming)
That was weird.
Well we got some letters.
You guys wanna join in
the letters, I guess not.
This first one is
from Joanne Ross.
I'll put that on still
story, you can see
the nice stickers and stuff.
Joanne says, dear
Mike and the robots,
hi, I love your show you guys
are the greatest, thanks.
Please do me a favor
if you get a chance,
would you please tell
my mom that Tom Servo
isn't related to ET.
Mom, Tom Servo is
not related to ET.
There's no relationship
whatsoever.
This next one is
from Kevin Mullins.
And it comes with a
nice little picture.
Put the letter up there.
It says dear Cambot
Incorporated, I would like
to see more Cambot on
the show, that's nice,
and if you say no I
will want to know why.
Cambot, you've been warned.
If Gypsy flies the ship why
doesn't she fly back to earth?
It's a good question, there's
no easy answers, Kevin.
Put that little picture
up, it's real sweet.
You can see, there's Crow
and there's Gypsy and Servo
and over here is
Boyd Gaines from
the old "One Day
at a Time" show.
So a real nice letter,
thanks Kevin and uh.
- [Robots] Two, one, go!
- Ah!
(chuckling)
Hey, what are you,
what's going on?
- All right, Mike.
We wanna hear you
promise you won't hunt
us down and stuff us and hang
us over the mantle piece.
- Well guys you know
I can't promise that.
(shouting)
Just kidding, I was
kidding you guys.
- Oh, I knew that.
- Back down to you
Dr. Florentine.
Come on here you little rascals.
- Whoa, whoa he's killing us.
- No I was.
(humming)
(bell chiming)
- Mother, dinner is ready.
Mom, dinner.
(laughing)
- Say Clay, nice spread.
What's the occasion?
- Don't be silly, Frank.
This is just our
typical evening meal.
Mother sit right.
- It looks great,
kid, it really does.
Don't get me wrong,
but well, Frank and I
are going out tonight.
- That's right, it's
thirsty Thursday's down
at the Tijuana Taxi Company.
(laughing)
- And I think I'll just stay
at the airport Ramada tonight.
I've got an early flight.
But I will see you at
the hearing, next month.
- Well, uh.
(clearing throat)
- Oh yes.
- Bye bye.
(giggling)
- Give me that!
(grunting)
(light music)
(screaming)